vladtv.com 2018-08-29

# VladTV // Privacy Policy

VLADTV may collect non-personally identifiable information regarding your visit to the Website. VLADTV may utilize third party software to collect this information and reserves the right to change its data collection methods, providers and/or software, at any time in its sole discretion.

_What Personal Information We Collect_

VLADTV may also collect Personal Information about you. By “Personal Information”, we mean information that can be used to identify a specific individual. This may include “cookies”.  Cookies are collected through our “Tracking Technologies” described below.  Other Personal Information is what you provide to us when registering for a service or purchasing a product.

By using the Website and providing any information to us, you are acknowledging that the Website is not a secure site and that data transmissions via email, upload through a network or on Website forms are inherently insecure. We will not intentionally disclose your Personal Information, but we cannot control and will not be liable interference by third-parties.  You agree not to provide any information through the Website or email that you would not want shared with others.

_How We Use Personal Information._

Cookie data use is addressed below under “Tracking Technologies”.

We will use your Personal Information to enable us to provide the service or product indicated when you provided the information.  We may also use your Personal Information to identify you when you visit our Website, to improve the operation and usefulness of our Website, to enable us to improve our services and products, and comply with applicable laws and law enforcement.

Users have the opportunity at any time to remove themselves from VladTV's communications by responding to the opt-out information provided on our Website and email broadcasts and/or calling 1-800-993-4032 and asking for Evan Hollins.

In the course of serving advertisements to the Website or other VLADTV platforms, our third-party advertisers may also collect information about you, or place or recognize a unique "cookie" or other tracking software on your browser, as described further below. Although VLADTV does not intend to conduct business with advertisers that use inappropriate or deceptive tracking techniques, VLADTV has no control over or responsibility for or control over the actions of our advertisers’ with respect to their own advertisements, data collection or handling policies, and accordingly VLADTV shall not have any liability with respect to the actions of advertisers on the Website. If you have any concerns, you should not access the advertiser link, ad or page.

_How We Protect Personal Information_

Personal information collected via the Website may be stored and processed in the United States and/or any other country in which VladTV maintains facilities, and by using the Website, you consent to any such storage, processing and transfer of information into and out of your country, state, and/or territory.

VladTV employs standard commercial procedural and technological measures reasonably designed to protect your Personal Information under our control from loss or unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. VladTV stores your personal information on secure computers located in a controlled access data center, to which only a small number of VladTV employees involved in the management of the data center have physical access. Where reasonably practical, VladTV uses encryption, firewalls, and other security technology to help prevent unauthorized access to your Personal Information.

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security and will not be liable for security breaches

_Tracking Technologies_

We use technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags, and scripts, to analyze trends, administer the Website, track users' movements around the Website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual and aggregated basis.

In addition to the other uses of Personal Information described herein, we use cookies to remember users' settings (e.g., language preference), and for authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Website, but your ability to use some features or areas of our Website may be limited.

VladTV employs a number of tracking technologies on its Website in order to improve our Website, products and services. Currently we use  ** _Google Analytics, New Relic, Disqus & Quantcast Choice_**. More information about this service may be located here: <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>, <https://newrelic.com/termsandconditions/privacy>, <https://help.disqus.com/terms-and-policies/disqus-privacy-policy> & <https://www.quantcast.com/terms/quantcast-choice-terms-of-service/>. 

_Data Retention_

You may request that we delete your Personal Information and after such request, we will retain and use your Personal Information only as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

_Contact For Any Privacy Concerns_

VladTV  
C/O Evan Hollins  
26500 Agoura Rd  
#102-845  
Calabasas CA 913022

Email:  

Phone:  
1-800-993-4032

VLADTV may also disclose your information: (1) if VLADTV determines a violation of the Terms has occurred; (2) if VLADTV believes such disclosure is necessary to identify or bring legal action regarding injury or interference with the rights of VLADTV or another user of the Web Site; (3) to respond to legal process or as otherwise required by law; and (4) to assist VLADTV in fraud protection or investigation.

You understand that information received from you may be used by VLADTV for any or all of the reasons described herein.

UNFORTUNATELY, INTENTIONAL DATA BREACHES AND UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS BY THIRD PARTIES IS A RISK THAT VLADTV CANNOT CONTROL.  WHILE VLADTV TAKES COMMERCIALLY REASONABLE STEPS TO PROTECT THE DATA IT STORES, IT CANNOT ASSUME RESPONSIBILTIY FOR SUCH THIRD PARTY ACTS. 

ACCORDINGLY, NONE OF THE VLADTV PARTIES SHALL HAVE ANY LIABILITY WHATSOEVER FOR ANY DATA BREACH OR UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO USER CONTENT OR OTHER INFORMATION ON OR SUBMITTED THROUGH THE WEB SITE, **REGARDLESS OF THE LEVEL OF CARE USED BY VLADTV**.

Except as otherwise required by law, any information submitted by you on the Web Site or in connection with your use of the Web Site, is not considered and will not be treated as confidential.
